classifiedads.com 2017-06-24

# Privacy Policy

_Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our website (the “Site”) and our products and services (the “Services”)._

## WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

When you visit the Site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and website use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse the Site.

**1\. Personal Information You Choose to Provide**

You can generally visit the Site without revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself, and you do not need an account to post listings, browse listings, or respond to listings.

If you choose to create an account and/or use our Services, we may collect personally identifiable information that you submit such as your name, contact data (address, email address, phone number) and other similar information. Likewise, we may also collect additional personally identifiable information that you voluntarily include in your listings or transmit with your communications to us.

The information that you provide when you post a listing is displayed in public areas and available to all visitors. Any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information, so please exercise caution. We also provide you with the option to submit pictures and/or a description of your item or service. When you post your listing on the Site, the description and pictures are displayed on the site and accessible to visitors on the Site.

If you provide personal information to a buyer or seller (either directly or by circumventing our messaging system), we have no control over how that information might be used by that individual. We recommend using our messaging system for any communications between you and potential buyers and sellers.

**2\. Web Site Use Information**

Similar to other commercial websites, the Site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and web server logs to collect information about how the Site is used. Information gathered through cookies and web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at the Site, and the websites visited just before and just after the Site. We, our advertisers and ad serving companies may also use small technology or pieces of code to determine which advertisements and promotions users have seen and how users responded to them.

## HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE TO US?

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering and expanding the Site and the Services. More specifically, we use personal information to provide the Services; provide customer service; troubleshoot problems; encourage safe buying and selling and enforce our policies; customize your experience, measure interest in our services, improve our services; and do other things for you as described when we collect the information. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to the Site and/or the Services.

We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties without your explicit consent. We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. We may also share personal information with service providers who help with our business operations, and third-party websites and publishers so the listings (or the content of the listings) published on the Site can also be published on a broader array of websites.

**What are Cookies?**

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a website, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies that originate from their sites. We have no access or control over those cookies.

**How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?**

As you use the Site, the website uses its cookies to differentiate you from other users. Cookies, in conjunction with our web server's log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting the Site and which parts of the Site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve the Site and better serve our customers. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not generally store any personal information that you provided to us in your cookies.

**Sharing Information with Third Parties**

The Site contains links to other websites on the Internet. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the information collection and use and privacy practices of such other websites and third parties. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every other website that may collect your personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by us from the Site.

We use third party companies to serve advertisements when you visit the Site. These companies may use information about your visits to the Site in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to the Site, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as pixel tags. Our privacy policy does not cover any use of information that a third-party ad-serving company may collect from you. These companies have their own policies as to record keeping and data retention. If you would like more information about this practice, or would like to know your choices about not having this information used by advertising companies, please click here: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>.

We use Google Analytics on the Site; information on how this collects and processes data can be found at: <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>. In addition, we have enabled certain Google Analytics advertising features that utilize cookies. These features enable us to obtain certain demographic and interests data for visitors to the Site. You can opt out of these features by visiting <https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads>.

We may use Google AdWords remarketing to trigger advertisements across the Internet. AdWords remarketing will display relevant ads tailored to you based on what parts of the Site you have viewed by placing a cookie on your machine. THIS COOKIE DOES NOT IN ANYWAY IDENTIFY YOU OR GIVE ACCESS TO YOUR COMPUTER. The cookie is used to say "This person visited this page, so show them ads relating to that page." Google AdWords remarketing allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you. If you do not wish to participate in our Google AdWords remarketing, you can opt out by visiting <https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/>.

In addition, we may enter into alliances, partnerships or other business arrangements with third parties who may be given access to personal information including your name, telephone number and email for the purpose of providing you information regarding certain products and services. When you make an inquiry about certain listings on the Site (e.g., used cars listings from dealers), you are expressly choosing to, and opting-in to, have us transfer your personally identifiable information to our third party service partners, and for such third party service partners to provide your personally identifiable information to other businesses who provide products or services that match your inquiry. The third party service partners may contact you regarding your inquiry.

As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or any dissolution.

**Notice of New Services and Changes**

Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to the Site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. As our customer, you will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers.

## HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?

**How Do We Secure Information Transmissions?**

We may employ procedural and technological security measures that are reasonably designed to help protect your personally identifiable information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. We may use secure socket layer and other security measures to help prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information.

**Certain Disclosures**

We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on us or affiliated parties; (b) protect and defend our rights and property, our site, the users of our site, and/or our affiliated parties; (c) act under circumstances to protect the safety of users of our site, us, or third parties.

**Your Consent**

By using the Site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on the Site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. If you have any questions, feel free to [contact us](https://www.classifiedads.com/feedback.php).

_Effective as of January 23, 2012_
